Guide to the Walter Thabit papers, 1950-2004
Thabit, Walter papers, 1950-2004
- Series VI. Studies
  - Study Proposals (SP)
    - SP-2: Youth Services Proposal (Box 6, Folder 11)
      A major effort to prepare a proposed study of indoor recreation which was approved but never funded
    - SP-3: New Business (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Describes a variety of efforts to do work for potential clients
    - SP-4: Miscellaneous Proposals (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - SP-5: Consulting Proposals (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - SP-6: Albany (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Efforts to undertake a rehabilitation study of an Albany neighborhood
    - SP-7: Cybersystem Research (Box 6, Folder 16)
      One of the attempts at joint venture which did not materialize.
    - SP-8: Lindenhurst (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Another joint venture to prepare a CBD (Central Business District) urban renewal plan
    - SP-9: Hoboken Pier Housing (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Preliminary work and a proposal to act as housing consultant for housing project. Never built
    - SP-10: Harlem Proposal (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Proposal to conduct an analysis and to plan for the 125th Street corridor in Harlem
    - SP-11: Williamsbridge Proposal (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Study of housing in a Bronx area, approved by community board but never funded by the Borough President
    - SP-12: Jamaica (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Became intrigued after a vacation to Jamaica to do planning work there. The British have it all wrapped up.
    - SP-13: Stamford Proposal (Box 6, Folder 22)
      Another Joint venture to do a series of housing and economic studies.
    - SP-14: Piers Area Proposal (Box 6, Folder 23)
      Worked with Architects Renewal Committee in Harlem to prepare this study proposal for redevelopment and upgrading of this industrial area along the Hudson north of 125th street
    - SP-15: Clinton Proposal (Box 6, Folder 24)
      A zoning study for the Clinton District of Manhattan
    - SP-16: Poughkeepsie Master Plan (Box 6, Folder 25)
      Jointly with Ralph Seligman with whom a lot of work was done in Hoboken
    - SP-17: Dataplan (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Scheme started in 1960 for developing a system for making color maps for cities in quantity so that Census and other data could be presented. Never fully developed at this time
    - SP-18: West Side Highway Proposal (Box 6, Folder 27)
      A joint venture in which we were to do the citizen participation sector. Thabit and his partners were not accepted by the state or city but the firm (Parsons) got the work when they dropped them.
  - Health (HE)
    - HE-1: Health Services Adm. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Mostly City programs and handouts
    - HE-2: Health Advocacy (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Various items of an advocacy nature
    - HE-3: Health- Original NENA Proposal (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Proposal for a local health care center
    - HE-4: Health Fac. Exp. CPC Studies (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Mostly hospital expansion studies
    - HE-5: Manitoba Health (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Quite good hospital program in Canada
    - HE-6: Narcotics (Box 27, Folder 10)
      A variety of materials on drug treatment including the staff's analysis
    - HE-7: Narcotics II (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - HE-8: Alcohol & Drug Treatment (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - HE-9: Mental Health (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Mostly resource documents
    - Health - Narcotics (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Education (ED)
    - ED-1: Schools- Planning (Box 27, Folder 14)
      Items of planning interest
    - ED-2: Sources of Information Regarding Day Care (Box 27, Folder 15)
      Sources and reports
    - ED-3: Parents for an Educational Park (Box 27, Folder 16)
      A hot topic in the late 60's, with racial integration as the primary objective
    - ED-4: Decentralization, Schools (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - ED-5: Education (Box 27, Folder 18)
      Various materials and reports, including one on decentralization
    - ED-6: Education II (Box 27, Folder 19)
      Various materials and reports, including decentralization
    - ED-7: Schools- Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - ED-8: Educational Facilities Labs. Newsletters (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - ED-9: Educational Facilities Labs. Newsletters II (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - ED-10: Educational Facilities Labs. Newsletters III (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - School Planning, 1997 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Charrette (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Educational Park (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Educational Park (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Spring Creek (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - School Decentralization (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Housing (HO)
    - HO-1: Housing (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - HO-2: MFY (Mobilizing for Youth) Contract (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - HO-3: Conservation- Rehabilitation (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - HO-4: Code Enforcement Conservation- Rehabilitation (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Early items including MFY (Mobilizing for Youth) Contract items
    - HO-5: Housing Costs (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - HO-6: Formation of HUD (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Bills before Congress plus Thabit's proposal for a much more sweeping Department of Development.
    - HO-7: HUD Sponsorship Requirements (Box 28, Folder 7)
      For non-profit housing sponsorship under Section 236
    - HO-8: HUD Requirements - 312, 115 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Rehab loan program
    - HO-9: Non-Profit Housing (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - HO-10: Housing & Renewal Law (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Various Bills before Congress
    - HO-11: Housing- Data Sources (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - HO-12: Low Rent Housing Problem III (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Various items including early writings of Walter Thabit.
    - HO-13: Housing Material (Box 28, Folder 13)
      A variety of domestic and international housing material
    - HO-14: Miscellaneous Housing (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - HO-15: Housing to 1973, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - HO-16: Housing to 1975, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - HO-17: Government Assisted Housing Materials (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Various housing program requirements and building codes.
    - HO-18: Public Housing - Eligibility Standards (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - HO-19: Turnkey Public Housing (Box 28, Folder 19)
      What it is and it's regulations
    - HO-20: Public Housing Photos and Drawings (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - HO-21: Housing Authority (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - HO-22: Delaney Report Critique (Box 28, Folder 22)
      Report on State low income housing program.
    - HO-23: Housing Production & Costs (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - HO-24: Rehabilitation & New Construction Programs (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - HO-25: HRB Research Reports (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Research on housing programs and integration efforts
    - HO-26: Housing Paper, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Various views on the city's housing efforts
    - HO-27: Industrialized Housing Studies (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - HO-28: Mobile Homes (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Mobile Homes statistics
    - HO-29: Mobile Homes II (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Mostly Thabit's analysis of mobile homes
    - HO-30: Housing for Undeveloped Areas (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Mass produced shelter for the very poorest countries
    - HO-31: Cooperative Housing (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Largely descriptive in the early years
    - HO-32: Housing Design (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Mostly public housing site plans
    - HO-33: The Low-Rent Problem and Public Housing I, early 1960s (Box 29, Folder 11)
      Housing materials and issues
    - HO-34: Low-Rent Housing Problem II, later 1960s (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - HO-35: Housing Paper II, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      More materials and analysis
    - HO-36: Logue Report (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Summary of and assessment of report on restructuring NYC housing efforts
    - HO-37: Housing Clippings/ Articles, through 1955 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - HO-38: Handicapped (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Paralyzed veterans flyer
    - HO-39: Rent Strike (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - HO-40: The Welfare Clients Fight (Box 29, Folder 18)
      Fight for better housing and benefits
    - HO-41: Recovery of the Unwanted (Box 29, Folder 19)
      Dealing with the hardest core poor
    - HO-42: Welfare- Housing (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - HO-43: Youth (Box 29, Folder 21)
      A survey of youth in East Flatbush.
    - HO-44: Aged- Housing (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - HO-45: Housing- Other Activism (Box 29, Folder 23)
      Various materials on local struggles
    - HO-46: Human Rights Hearing- Redlining (Box 29, Folder 24)
      Testimony before Commission on Human Rights.
    - Housing I (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Housing - Various Files (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Early Housing Papers (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Housing Policies for Depressed Areas (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Integration Article (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Core (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Race In Housing (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Redlining/Aged/Welfare - HSG (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Welfare/Rent Strikes (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Urban Renewal (RE)
    - RE-1: Structuring Urban Renewal (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - RE-2: Community Planning Design (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Includes A couple of items not dealing with community planning
    - RE-3: CD VII Budget For New York City, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - RE-4: OEO Proposals (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Various proposals for poverty programs
    - RE-5: Model Cities File- General (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Mostly citizen participation in Model Cities
    - RE-6: Community Renewal Notes (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Urban renewal and community renewal items
    - RE-7: Model Cities File- General (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Structure and evaluations
    - RE-8: Urban Renewal (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - RE-9: NYC Vacancies/Demolition Statistics (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - RE-10: Relocation Study 1953 NYC, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Mostly maps
    - RE-11: Relocation (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - RE-12: Commercial Relocation (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Social Welfare (SW)
    - SW-1: Urabn Sociology (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - SW-2: Notes on Crime (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - SW-3: Manpower and General urban Center Information (Box 30, Folder 15)
      Job Training
    - SW-4: The Izumi Papers (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Urban environment writings by an MIT colleague
    - SW-5: Manpower, Jobs, Training (Box 30, Folder 17)
      Much about racism in the job and training market
    - SW-6: Migrant Labor (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - SW-7: Notes on People (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - SW-8: Social Welfare (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Social Welfare (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Planning Organization (PO)
    - PO-1: Planning Education (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - PO-2: Metropolitan Planning (Box 30, Folder 22)
      Much on the debate in the 1950's and 1960's; how to go about it.
    - PO-3: Regional Planning (New York Region) (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - PO-4: Columbia- Habitat Forum/Tri-state conference (Box 30, Folder 24)
      Inner city discussion on a tri-state agenda
    - PO-5: Organization & Administration (Box 30, Folder 25)
      More on organizing and running planning operations
    - PO-6: Metropolitan Government, State (Box 30, Folder 26)
      Includes New York City as a State
  - Subject Files (SU)
    - SU-1: Urban Economics (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SU-2: Pollution (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - SU-3: Cable TV (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - SU-4: Water & Sewers (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - SU-5: Misc. to be Filled (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - SU-6: Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - SU-7: Planning Techniques (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Mapping, population forecasting, economic base, other
    - SU-8: Industrial Survey- NYC (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Consultant report on survey of industrial areas in New York City.
    - SU-9: Hatch- Industrial High Tech. (Box 31, Folder 9)
      Dynamic mix of small manufacturing enterprises
    - SU-10: Industrial- Theory (Box 31, Folder 10)
      How to study industrial land use
    - SU-11: Public Outdoor Recreation (Box 31, Folder 11)
      Regional, City, other.
    - SU-12: Public Recreation (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - SU-13: Transportation- Traffic (Box 31, Folder 13)
      Mostly Highway Planning
    - SU-14: Traffic & Transportation (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - SU-15: Master Planning Theory (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - SU-16: Zoning for New York City, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      Mostly on the 1961 rezoning.
    - SU-17: Cuba- Land Use (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - SU-18: Retail Trade (Box 31, Folder 18)
      Mostly on Baltimore planning for retail trade
    - SU-19: Downtown Article (Box 31, Folder 19)
      Various items on downtown planning
    - Integration (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Squatters Fight (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Racism - Civil Rights (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Homefront (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Subject Files - Misc. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Blockbuster/Racism (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Misc. III (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Recovery of the Unwanted (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Outdoor Recreation (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Organizing for Planning (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Industrial Planning (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Transportation Planning (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Nuclear Weapons (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Civil Defense (opposition to) (CD)
    - CD-1: Effects of Nuclear Weapons- 1962, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      Articles and other materials describing the destructive capabilities of H bombs
    - CD-2: Nuclear- Library (Box 31, Folder 21)
      Articles, publications
    - CD-3: Anti- Nuclear 1982- Organizing, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      Articles, clippings, etc., in pursuit of nuclear disarming in 1982
    - CD-4: Nuclear 1982- Other Efforts (Box 31, Folder 23)
      More clippings, position papers
    - CD-6: Nuclear Policy Statements by planners and other groups, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - CD-7: Community Disarmament Budget Manual (Box 32, Folder 2)
      One national budget and a start on a local community budget that was never completed.
  - Miscellaneous (MI)
    - MI-1: Books I, II, III (Box 38, Folder 1)
      Flyers of books and more
    - MI-2: Books I, II, III (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - MI-3: Books I, II, III (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - MI-4: Fresh Meadows (Box 38, Folder 4)
      One of two writing jobs Thabit did for Voorhees, Walker, Smith, Smith and Haines
    - MI-5: The Telephone Story- Article 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      The second article.
    - MI-5a: The Telephone Story- Article 2 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - MI-6: Zeitlin Review (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Review of a Morris Zeitlin book.
    - MI-7: Housing Planning and Maintenance (Box 38, Folder 8)
      A housing course aborted for lack of enrollment.
    - MI-8: Research and Survey Course- Materials (Box 38, Folder 9)
      Course given at Long Island University
    - MI-9: Commercial -Industrial Renewal (Box 38, Folder 10)
      Materials for a planning course given at the New School
    - MI-10: Morningside Renewal Course (Box 38, Folder 11)
      Course given to local community group.
    - MI-11: Urban Renewal- Problems and Practices (Box 38, Folder 12)
      Renewal course taught at The New School
    - MI-12: Bibliographies (Box 38, Folder 13)
      Course bibliographies of others
    - MI-13: Physical Planning Course CUNY Hunter (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - MI-14: Community Planning Design, New School, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - MI-15: Urbanism Program (Box 38, Folder 16)
      An abortive attempt to start an urban institute at The New School. Eventually started by others.
    - MI-16: Res. & Survey Course Materials (Box 38, Folder 17)
      Long Island University
    - MI-17: Hunter/Physical Planning NOTES (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - MI-18: Hunter Comprehensive Studio Course (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - MI-19: COSMOS Rehabilitation Course (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Part of LID(League for Industrial Democracy) Leadership Development Program.
    - MI-20: Rockefeller Letter (Box 38, Folder 21)
      Unfinished article on how to make public housing acceptable. Nelson Rockefeller's request
    - MI-21: Leadership Training Institute (Box 38, Folder 22)
      A course organized by PEO (Planners for Equal Opportunities) for the LID (League for Industrial Democracy)
    - MI-22: Course Materials (Box 38, Folder 23)
      From other course not prepared by Thabit.
    - MI-23: Koch- Forest Hills (Box 38, Folder 24)
      Correspondence on a proposed public housing project
    - MI-24: New York Civic Center (Box 38, Folder 25)
      Material and commentary on proposed plan
    - MI-25: Bronx Housing Committee (Box 38, Folder 26)
      Helping local group develop housing policy statement
    - MI-26: South Street Seaport (Box 38, Folder 27)
      Supporting its creation
    - MI-27: 49th-50th St Municipal Garage (Box 38, Folder 28)
      An opposition group seeking support
    - MI-28: Breezy Point (Box 38, Folder 29)
      Opposition to the private development of a beach area
    - MI-29: Citizens Committee vs. Lindsay Riverdale (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - MI-30: West Village (Box 38, Folder 31)
      Jane Jacobs' innovative plan for 5 story housing in the West Village.
    - MI-31: Cadman Plaza (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Opposition to more redevelopment
    - MI-32: 3rd St. Coffee Houses Fight (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - MI-33: Tompkins Square Housing Plan (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - MI-34: Metro North in East Harlem Materials (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - MI-35: Washington Market Area (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Study Proposal
    - MI-36: Tree Planting Ordinance (Box 39, Folder 6)
      Championed by Charles Abrams
    - MI-37: Who Owns New York (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Several radical writings on housing
    - MI-38: Copake Report (Box 40, Folder 2)
      An analysis of the town's zoning ordinance
    - MI-39: Waterside (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Controversy over a proposed housing project on filled East River land
    - MI-40: Sutton Area Committee (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Local area group that demanding more restrictive zoning; related to Planning board #6 zoning study, "Downzoning for Survival"
    - MI-41: LENA (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Lower East Side Neighborhood Association/METCOP (Metropolitan Committee on Planning) planning effort leading to involvement with Cooper Square renewal
    - MI-42: Seligaman - Land Use Course (Box 45, Folder 7)
      Thabit helped for one term
    - MI-43: Apartment Planning (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Sketches
    - MI-44: 115th St. Block Project (Box 45, Folder 9)
      Historical Approach to block development
    - MI-45: Quebec (Box 45, Folder 10)
      Materials for analysis of an area which never took off.
    - WTC Civic Alliance Charrette (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - City Planning 9/11 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Progress Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Hoboken - Various (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Delta Proposal - Puerto Rico (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Committee on Civil Rights - 16 Alabama Counties (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Anti-Poverty - Theory (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Civil Rights (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Anti-Poverty Notes (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Radicals in the Professions (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - "Walter Thabit - Design Arts" Report (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Rent Control (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Fort Hamilton (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Lynch's Glen Island Estate (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - White Plains (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Course Materials (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Sid Willis - Jersey Studies (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Fresh Meadows / ATT Article (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Manhattan Esplanade (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Citywide CD Maps (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Park and 33rd - Subpoena (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Corruption/Misc. (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Administrative (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Graphic Design (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - New Street/City Hall (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Rulers (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Piven - Davidoff Debate (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Planning Proposals (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Planning Proposals (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Core Raleigh Kit (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - National Committee on Full Emp. (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Defensible Space (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Thabit Advocacy Writings (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Howard Samuels Campaign (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Political Campaigns (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Next City Corporation (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Logue Report (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Misc. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Alpa (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - MFY (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Brochure Materials (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Metropolitan Dev./State NYC (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Garden of Eden (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - 701 Program (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Legal and Economic Mech.'s (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Articles and Reviews (AR)
    - AR-1: Colliers 1968 Year Book, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      Materials used in preparing an article on the state of urban affairs in 1968 for the Collier Year Book
    - AR-2: Crowell Collier Articles, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      1967 article and materials
    - AR-3: Defensible Space Review (Box 40, Folder 25)
      A critical review of Oscar newman's indefensible book
    - AR-4: Columbia Cit. Part. Paper (Box 40, Folder 26)
      At the planning school's invtation
    - AR-5: Miscellaneous One - Page (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Letters to the Editor, etc.
    - AR-6: Economic Development (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - AR-7: Village Voice Reviews (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - AR-8: Reviews, Other (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - AR-9: Various Articles (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - AR-10: Bahr Review Skid Row (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - AR-11: Restructuring The Planning Function (Box 41, Folder 7)
      Articles on Planning
    - AR-12: AIP Journal Reviews (Box 41, Folder 8)
      American Institute of Planning
  - Rent Control (RC)
    - RC-1: Rent Control - Law - Regulations (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - RC-2: Rent Control 1967, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - RC-3: Rent Control 1965, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - RC-4: Rent Control Analysis - Data (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - RC-5: Rent Control Statistics - 1965 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - RC-6: Philadelphia Rent Control (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - RC-7: RAND Report - Welfare Rents (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - RC-8: MBR - Rent Increase (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - RC-9: Rent Control Statement (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - RC-10: Rent Control - 1969, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Surveys (SF)
    - SF-1: Canadian Historic Survey (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - SF-2: Non - Thabit Housing Conditions (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - SF-3: Ladies Mile (Box 44, Folder 10)
      Landmark Survey
    - SF-4: Planning Survey Book - Pub Review (Box 44, Folder 11)
      Bibliographies
    - SF-5: Miscel./Model Letter/Schedule/Analysis (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - SF-6: Freeprot - Topics Data (Box 44, Folder 13)
      Traffic Stuff
    - SF-7: Housing Inspections, Newark (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - SF-8: Brownsville Resident Survey (Box 44, Folder 15)
      Deals with children's needs.
    - SF-9: 175 Union (Box 44, Folder 16)
      Rehabilitation Evaluation from Union Street Project
    - SF-10: 188 Union (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - SF-11: 12 South Bridge (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - SF-12: 37 South Bridge (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - SF-13: 48 South Bridge (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - SF-14: 8 South Perry (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - SF-15: 27 South Perry (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - SF-16: 29 South Perry (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - SF-17: 8 Grand (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - SF-18: 9 Grand (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - SF-19: 10 Grand (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - SF-20: Rehab Standards HUD & Municipal Loan (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - SF-21: Hartford Tenant Interviews - UA 3/73, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - SF-22: MFY Housing Forms (Box 44, Folder 29)
      Mobilization for Youth housing compaint, organizing and building operations forms
    - SF-23: Guidelines - Survey Materials (Box 44, Folder 30)
      For evaluation of prospective landmarks
    - SF-24: Legal Economics Study (Box 44, Folder 31)
      Monitoring a consultant study prepared for the Landmarks Preservation Commission
    - SF-25: Cooper Square Surveys (Box 44, Folder 32)